Guide to the Greentree Stud and Stable Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs, 1931-1986, undated; Series III
  - Horses
    - Bud Lerner-Basquaise, 1932-1933, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Bunting-Saunaugha, Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Capot, 1949, undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Oversize (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Casse Noisette, Undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Chance Play-Ladina, Undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Chance Play-Piga, Undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Cherry Fizz, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Chicle-Goose Egg, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Chicle-Hoity Toity, 1932, undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Chicle-Panache, Undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Chicle-Pandawdy, 1933, undated (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Chicle-Robin's Egg, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Chicle-Spring Cleaning, 1933, undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Closed Season, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Cohoes, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Cooling Out Hots, Undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Count Pennies (oversize), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Cudgel-Alicia, Undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Dance Cap, Undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Dancing Lesson, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Devil Diver, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Diavala-Allepena, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Diavala-Petranella, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Dis Dane-All Callas, 1933-1935 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Dis Dane-Conge, 1933, undated (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Dominant-Bittersweet, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Dominant-Delicacy, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Dominant-Dippy, 1933, undated (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Dominant-Fresnay, Undated (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - Dominant-Hoity Toity, Undated (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - Douce France, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Duck Heaven, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Eclipse, Undated (Box 38, Folder 55)
    - El Gaucho, Undated (Box 38, Folder 56)
    - Eurasia, 1959-1962, undated (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - Europa, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 58)
    - Expression, Circa 1944 (Box 38, Folder 59)
    - First Rose, Circa 1949 (Box 38, Folder 60)
    - Foolish Pleasure, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 61)
    - Fools Gold, Circa 1961 (Box 38, Folder 62)
    - Francoise, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 63)
    - Gangplank, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Gettysburg, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Golden Fragrance, Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Grand Ace-Diksabrule, 1933, undated (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
    - Guillotine, 1949, circa 1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Hatchet Man, Undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Hilla, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Hilwan, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Horse Schooling, Undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - How's Tricks, Circa 1953 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Humaya, Circa 1947 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Jitterbug, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - John Jacob, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - J.P. Grier-Bonus, Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - J.P. Grier-Chinty, Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - J.P. Grier-Shrine, Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Key to the Mint, Circa 1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Knot Hole, Circa 1952 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Lacking JWP, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Late Act (oversize), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Le Midi, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Lonely Cloud, Undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Locoweed, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Macau-Cannubert, 1933, undated (Box 39, Folder 24-25)
    - Macau-Piga, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Mad Hatter-Bonus, Undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Mad Hatter-Hoity Toity, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Mad Hatter-Lady Be Good, Circa 1933 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Mad Hatter-Leopardess, Circa 1933, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Mad Hatter-Lodina, Circa 1932 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Mad Hatter-Pandawdy, Undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Mad Hatter-Shrine Chestnut Colt, Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Mad Hatter-Tip Top, Circa 1932-1935, undated (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Malacious, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Mea Lap, Undated (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Melodious, Circa 1950 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Metropolitan Handicap, Undated (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Middle Watch, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Moulette, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - My Sin, Circa 1953 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Night Game, Circa 1949 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Northern Star, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Old Game, Circa 1954 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Ooweekin, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Open Question, Circa 1948 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Outing Class (oversize), Circa 1960 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Paddleduck, 1948-Circa 1949 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Paoluccio, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Pass Hey, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Pennant-Crispenna, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Pennant-Sunday Best, Circa 1932-1933 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Pennant-Twaddle, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Pennant-Untidy, Circa 1934-1935 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Persian Road, Undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Peter Pan-Brimay, Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Peter Pan-Sunday Best, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Piguet, Circa 1940 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Pincole, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Pinnace, Circa 1947 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Pop Corn, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Prank, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Prince Pal-Bittersweet, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Princess Palitana, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Pure Whiskey, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Questionnaire, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Quickmarch, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Rare Bloom, Circa 1937 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Register, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Romaunt, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Royal Minstrel-False Modesty, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Royal Minstrel-Glade, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Royal Minstrel-Lazy Daisy, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Royal Minstrel-Lazy Susan, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Royal Minstrel-Leopardess, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Royal Minstrel-Leopardess, Ruddy Duck, Rinky, Undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Royal Minstrel-Lodma, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Royal Minstrel-Perhaps So, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Royal Minstrel-Prudish, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Royal Minstrel-Red Red Rose, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Royal Minstrel-Ruddy Duck, Circa 1937 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Royal Minstrel-Untidy, Circa 1932 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Ruddy, Circa 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Rudolph, Circa 1960 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - School Tie, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Shower Gold, Undated (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Shut Out, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Sickle-Tree Top, Undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Silly Question, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Solar Myth, Circa 1956 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Space Happy, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Stage Door Johnny, Circa 1968 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Star Bout, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Saint Brideaux-Allepena, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - St. Brideaux-Homely, 1935 March 27 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - St. Brideaux-Maracaiba, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - St. Brideaux-Tassabant, Undated (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - St. Brideaux-Welcome Gift, 1935 April 5 (Box 40, Folder 50)
    - St. Germans-Bonus, 1935 March 29 (Box 40, Folder 51)
    - St. Germans-Crocus, Circa 1933 (Box 40, Folder 52)
    - St. Germans-False Modesty, Undated (Box 40, Folder 53)
    - St. Germans-Glade, Undated (Box 40, Folder 54)
    - St. Germans-Leopardess, Undated (Box 40, Folder 55)
    - St. Germans-Panache, Undated (Box 40, Folder 56)
    - St. Germans-Red Red Rose, Undated (Box 40, Folder 57)
    - St. James-Cressida, Undated (Box 40, Folder 58)
    - St. James-Tree Top, Undated (Box 40, Folder 59)
    - Stop the Music, Undated (Box 40, Folder 60)
    - Stormy Cruise, Circa 1951 (Box 40, Folder 61)
    - Stout Graft, Undated (Box 40, Folder 62)
    - Sunday Evening, Circa 1950 (Box 40, Folder 63)
    - Swallow Hawk, 1936 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 64)
    - Tailspin, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Tambo (oversized), 1943 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Tangleweed, Circa 1951 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Tea Olive, Undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Tehriva, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - The Axe, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - The Porter-Fair Faint, Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - The Porter-Fleeting Dawn, Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - The Porter-Kenya, 1935 March 27 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Three and Two, Circa 1950 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Third Degree (oversized), 1939 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Tom Fool, Undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Toronja, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Toto, Circa 1951 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Trial Balloon, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Tudor Princess, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Tungsten, Undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Tutankhamen, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Twink Alicia, 1935 March 27 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Twinkle Twinkle, 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Upset-Fair Faint, Circa 1932 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Upset-Goose Egg, Circa 1932 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Upset-Ravage, Undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Upset-Upsedaisy, Circa 1932 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Vito-Penumbra, Circa 1933 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Weatherwise, 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - What's New, Circa 1941 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Whichone-High Climb, Circa 1932 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Whichone-Homely, Circa 1933 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Why the Rush, Circa 1949 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Wildair-Caradmine, Undated (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Wildair-Cherry Bounce, Undated (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Wildair-La Religieux, Undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Yes or No, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Oversized (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - People
    - Employees, Undated (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Whitney, Helen Hay, Undated (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Property
    - Greentree Stables (Red Bank, New Jersey), Undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Greentree Stud (Lexington, Kentucky), 1931, undated (Box 41, Folder 38-39)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Racing
    - Flash Stakes, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Reports and Meeting Minutes, 1932-1994; Series IV
  - Reports
    - Annual
      - General, 1957-1980 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
      - Directors, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Treasurer's, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
    - Breeding, 1983-1989 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Farm
      - General, 1955-1958 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Greentree Stable (Lexington, Kentucky), 1938-1942 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        Includes financial reports.
      - Horses, 1987-1994 (Box 45, Folder 4-7)
  - Meeting minutes
    - Stockholders and Directors
      Includes minutes and supporting documentation of the meetings of the stockholders and directors of Llangollen Stable, Inc., Mare's Nest Stud, Inc., and Greentree Stud, Inc.
      - 1932-1950 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
      - 1951-1964 (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
      - 1965-1972 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
      - 1973-1982 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Greentree Stud and Stable Advisory Committee minutes and final report, 1983-1994 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
- Topical, 1903-1995; Series V
  - Horses
    - Appraisal of John Hay Whitney horses, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Bloodmare study, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Boarding fees, 1985-1994 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
    - Breeders Cup, 1984-1994 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Breeding
      General
      See also: Reference binder on breeding, box 54, folders 4-7.
      - Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1974-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Stock, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Change in Location or Status of Horses forms, 1982-1989 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Evaluations, 1944-1949 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Family trees, Undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Foal memoranda, 1932-1934, 1982-1993 (Box 52, Folder 3-14)
    - Genealogies, 1936-1939 (Box 52, Folder 15-16)
    - Inventories, 1930-1936, 1975-1999 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Matchmakers (breeders' exchange), 1984-1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Purchases, 1986-1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - "The Quest for a Classic Winner", Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Races
      - Notes, Undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - "Record of Races Won"
        See: Series II, Financial, Ledgers, Circa 1924-1930, box 6, folder 1.
      - Statements/reports
        - 1929, 1972-1985 (Box 53, Folder 6-9)
        - 1986-1994 (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
    - Reference, 1955, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 4-7)
    - Stallion services
      - Purchased, 1985-1990 (Box 55, Folder 1-5)
      - Sold
        - 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 6-9)
        - 1987-1988 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
        - 1989-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1-8)
    - Sales, 1969-1995
      Includes transactions of horses bought and sold by Greentree Stud or associated business partners.
      - Correspondence and invoices, 1982-1995 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
      - Horse record ledger, 1969-1977, 1983-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 4-6)
    - Sold, 1989-1994 (Box 59, Folder 1-6)
    - Stud fees, 1983-1994 (Box 59, Folder 7-9)
    - Syndicates
      - General, 1959-1969 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Arts and Letters, 1970-1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Caro, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Chief's Crown, 1985-1994 (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
      - Ends Well
        - General, 1985-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - Agreement, 1985-1994 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - Interest payments, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - Payments, other, 1986-1989 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Shareholders
          - Andrews, Paul, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
          - Bailie, Sally Ann, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
          - Bandoroff, Craig, Charles Boden, and Walter Kelley, 1986-1991 (Box 62, Folder 3)
          - Barrett, William L., 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 4)
          - Berkshire Stud, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 5)
          - Cygnet, Ellis partnership, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 6)
          - DiBonaventura, Chris, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
          - DiBonaventura, Peter, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
          - Dresden Farm, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
          - Fallstaff Breeders Association, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 10)
          - Gallagher's Farm, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 11)
          - Hallenbeck, Prentiss W., 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 12)
          - Joe's Lil Girl, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 13)
          - Kayo, William, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 14)
          - Londin, Jean and Jerome, 1985-1988 (Box 62, Folder 15)
          - McGrath, John, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 16)
          - Milfer Farm, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
          - Morrell & Raymond, 1987-1990 (Box 62, Folder 18)
          - Neilson, Gerald, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 19)
          - Nolan, Howard, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 20)
          - Raymond, Tim and Sam Morell, 1987-1993 (Box 62, Folder 21)
          - Reinacher, Robert, Jr., 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 22)
          - Rolfe, Ronald S., 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 23)
          - Schoenborn, Ellen, 1985-1991 (Box 62, Folder 24)
          - Schoenborn, Gus, Jr., 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 25)
          - Schoenborn, Gus, Sr., 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 26)
          - Schwartz, Barry, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 27)
          - Taylor, Frank, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 28)
          - TCB Construction Corporation, 1986-1992 (Box 62, Folder 29)
          - Topnotch Farm & Fox Crossing Farm, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 30)
          - Wilmot, William, 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 31)
      - Fred Astaire
        - General, 1987-1994 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Shareholders
          - Blanche Levy Stable (B & R Partners), 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
          - Centennial Farm, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
          - Couch, George (Hichclere, Incorporated), 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
          - Dearborn, Limited, 1988-1992 (Box 63, Folder 7)
          - Elser, Christopher (Hichclere, Incorporated), 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 8)
          - Goetz, J. Nicholas, 1981-1987 (Box 63, Folder 9)
          - Hansen, Robert and Joan, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 10)
          - Hettinger, John (Akindale Farm), 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 11)
          - Kidder, Charles and Lawrence, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 12)
          - Koch, Doug, Dum (Berkshire Stud), 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 13)
          - Lavin Blockstock Services, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 14)
          - Mallory, Dan (Meadowhaven Farm), 1987-1994 (Box 63, Folder 15)
          - Mangurian, Harry (Mockingbird Farm), 1987-1992 (Box 63, Folder 16)
          - Marcia Schott Partnership, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 17)
          - McMakin, Nelson, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 18)
          - Meadowview Farm, 1987-1991 (Box 64, Folder 1)
          - Moran, Elizabeth (Brushwood Stable), 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 2)
          - Nelson, Dale (Hawkeye Thoroughbred), 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
          - Pineau, A Lenord, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
          - Reinacher, Robert, Jr., 1987-1991 (Box 64, Folder 5)
          - Roberston, Scott, 1987-1992 (Box 64, Folder 6)
          - Schoenborn, Gus, Jr. and Michael Shanely, 1987-1992 (Box 64, Folder 7)
          - Sexton, Hargus, 1987-1989 (Box 64, Folder 8)
          - Spagnoli, William, 1987-1992 (Box 64, Folder 9)
          - Spreckels, Lois (Corrington Farms), 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 10)
          - Vintage Farms, Incorporated, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 11)
          - Walden, Ben, Jr., 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
          - Walden, Ben, Jr./Madden, Patrick and Preston, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 13)
          - Walden, Ben, Sr., 1987-1991 (Box 64, Folder 14)
          - West, Robert S. (Milford Farm), 1987-1991 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - Tom Fool, 1953-1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Sovereign Dancer, 1984-1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Trainers
      - Badgett, William, 1990-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Baker, James D., 1990 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Training, 1984-1994 (Box 65, Folder 5-6)
  - Publicity
    - Clippings
      - 1903-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1-21)
      - 1962-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1-10)
      - 1972-1984 (Box 68, Folder 1-6)
      - Undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Films
      Includes correspondence and files relating to film projects about the farm.
      - Greentree Thoroughbred, 1972-1982 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Thoroughbred (NBC documentary), 1964-1980 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Press release, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Scrapbooks
      - General, 1930 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Memories of the Kentucky Derby, 1931 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - No Robbery, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Racing commissions and associations
    Includes correspondence, applications, and other requirements related to membership. Membership in racing organizations and compliance with state commissions are requirements to race thoroughbred horses in the United States.
    - California, 1961-1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Florida, 1954-1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Jockey Club, 1959-1994 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Keeneland Association, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Kentucky, 1970-1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles Turf Club, 1951-1968 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Maryland, 1954-1983 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Maryland Jockey Club, 1952-1974 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - New Jersey, 1963-1982 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - New York, 1953-1989 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - New York Racing Association
      - General, 1966-1995 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Pension Plan, 1970-1981 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Queens County Jockey Club, 1953-1954 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - United Hunts Racing Association, 1932-1952 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Westchester Racing Association, 1952-1955 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate
    - Greentree Stable (Aiken, South Carolina)
      - General, 1946-1951 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Pitfield House, 1928-1947 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Ocala Annex (Ocala, Florida)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Maintenance, 1961-1969 (Box 71, Folder 4-6)
      - Mortgage, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Royal Ascot scrapbook, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilia, 1921-1979, undated (Box 72, Folder 3-4)
- Additional Materials, 1926-2000; Accession 2011-M-064
  The accession consists of correspondence and financial and legal files maintained by Shearman & Sterling. The records provide a financial and legal picture of the organization from 1983, when Betsey Cushing Whitney became sole owner, until 1994. The organization's finances, dissolution, and sales of assets are particularly well documented.
  The records are organized into five sections: Correspondence, Financial, Meetings, Tax material, and Topical. Within each section the records are arranged in the order maintained by Shearman & Sterling, Betsey Cushing Whitney's legal consul.
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1982 June 25-1995 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
    - Carswell, Robert, 1979-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Redemption of Greentree Stud Stable, 1976 August 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Financial
    - Statements of assets, liability, and capital
      - 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
      - 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - Audited financials, 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - Greentree document structural regarding audit inquiry letter received from Rosie L. James, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Accounting procedures and controls, 1984 April (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Financial forecast business plan by Scott Blanchard to Greentree Stud Committee, 1983 March 4 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Meetings
    - Board of Directors special meeting, 1982 October 15 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Annual meeting, 1986 March 11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Annual meeting report, 1989 June 6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Committee
      - Minutes
        - 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7-10)
        - 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
      - Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4-5)
  - Tax material
    - American Horse Council, Tax Bulletin, Newsletter, and other publications, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Background to legal research/material for scenarios involving grandchildren in a family horse breeding business, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Schedule and Form 4797, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Jerome Caulfield memorandum on tax plan, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Court of Appeals Case 83-2014, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Topical
    - Saratoga Harness Racing complaint correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Churchill Downs correspondence, 1984-1985, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Beckhampton, Ltd.
      - Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
      - Sale--document structural regarding estate of John Hay Whitney, 1983 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Spendthrift Farm, private placement, 1983 April (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Equine Syndications," brochure by American Horse Council, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Structural regarding Betsey Cushing Whitney's contracts with Robert J. Reinacher, Jr., Perry Alexander, and Jeremy Tree, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Research on cases under Code Section 183, 1962-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Agreement draft between Betsey Cushing Whitney and William Badgett, Jr., 1994 May (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Horses in training list, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Dispersement of stock and newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Statement by Betsey Cushing Whitney of dissolution, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Breeding division reports, 1994 February-March (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Financial information, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Committee agenda, 1994 January 26 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Appraisal summary, 1994 January 12 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Projections, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)